

MD ZEESHAN RAZA

ELECTRICAL AND ELECTRONICS ENGINEER

CONTACT

7449671033



zshnreza@gmail.com



43/C Topsia Road, Kolakata-700039



https://www.linkedin.c om/in/zeeshan-raza-34224417b

EXPERTISE SKILLS

- C
- C++
- AWS Cloud
- M.S Office

LANGUAGE

English

German

Hindi

Bengali

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE 01

I'm an Electrical and Electronics Engineer with three year of Industrial working experience. My goal is to work in an organization that offers a learning in a challenging environment with a scope of individual development and offers attractive perspective of career growth.

EDUCATION 02

Pursuing - B-TECH IN ELECTRICAL & ELECTRONICS ENGINEERING

MAKAUT (2020 - 2023)

• 89% Till 6th Semester

DIPLOMA IN ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING

Shree Ramkrishna Institute of Science and Technology

- 2016 2019

BODHICARIYA SR. SECONDARY SCHOOL (2014)

- Board- C.B.S.E
- CGPA- 5.0

03

EXPERIENCE

Bharat Petroleum Corporation LTD. APRIL 2021 - MAY 2022

APPRENTICESHIP

- Production
- Engineering & Maintanance
- · Packaging & Dispatch
- Logistics

SELF-ASSESSMENT

HOBBIES

- · Reading books
- Playing cricket
- Travelling

NATURE

- Dynamic
- Responsible
- Adaptive

STRENGTH

- · High self esteem
- · Goal oriented
- · Can work extra hours

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Projects Voltmeter using Arduino.
- Participated in Tech Fest.
- · Blood Donation.
- Participated in Relief Camps to be a Part of the Relief Work Team.
- Participated in Quiz Competition.

EXPERIENCE

Amazon Teleperformance SEPTEMBER 2020 - MARCH 2021

CUSTOMER SERVICE ACCIOCATE (CSA)

- Dedicated to service improvement
- Require strong communication skill and
- telecommunication language
- · Learned to maintain high level of
- · professionalism, patience and efficiently
- · minimizing customer dissatisfaction and
- · increasing customer loyalty

BOOK LINC

2014 - 2016

SALES REPRESENTATIVE

- Efficient and effective
- · Client handling
- Organizing and Managing business
- Contact new and existing customers to meet
- and exceed sales objectives.
- Organize, rotate, and stock shelves during
- each store visit.
- · Negotiate and use persuasion skills to
- · overcome objections.

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that all the above mentioned information are true in my belief. I hope you will consider my application in favour and appoint me.

Your Sincerely,
MOHAMMAD ZEESHAN RAZA